<resources>
    <string name="main_title">BreakScape</string>
    <string name="security_alert">Security Alert!\nSecurity Alert!\nSecurity Alert!</string>
    <string name="start_btn">Start</string>
    <string name="leaders_btn">Leaderboard</string>
    <string name="exit_btn">Exit</string>
    <string name="opt1">Phishing</string>
    <string name="opt2">Passwords</string>
    <string name="opt3">Encryption</string>
    <string name="opt4">Internet of things</string>

    <string name="phising1">It\'s one of the oldest types of cyberattacks,
        dating back to the 1990s, and still one of the most widespread and pernicious. This cyber
        attack that uses disguised email as a weapon. The goal is to trick the email recipient into
        believing that the message is something they want or need — a request from their bank,
        for instance, or a note from someone in their company — and to click a link or download an
        attachment. The attackers masquerade as a trusted entity.</string>
    <string name="phising2">If you click on show me the emails button, you will be able to see a
        selection of different emails that I\'ve been sending to your company. There is 12 examples
        where only 4 are spam. Please, identify the spam emails and you will have the four digits
        that will help you to complete this puzzle.</string>
    <string name="pass1">Password protection is a security process that protects information
        accessible via computers that needs to be protected from certain users. Password protection
        allows only those with an authorized password to gain access to certain information.</string>
    <string name="pass2">By researching on the people who works in your company, I was able to see
        how bad the passwords were. In this puzzle, I have set an easy password from one of your key workers.
        Check the information button and see if you can find it as easy as I did.</string>
    <string name="encryption1">Encryption explanation</string>
    <string name="encryption2">In this puzzle, I wanted to make more difficult for you to fix my work,
    so I have encrypted all the texts. I have provided 4 pictures that should be familiar to you.
        Let\'s see if you are able to get the code that will resolve this puzzle.</string>
    <string name="usb1">Most modern mobile devices allow you to connect peripheral devices such as
        external hard drives, printers and cameras using short range wireless connections like
        Bluetooth, or physical interfaces, such as USB and Thunderbolt.</string>
    <string name="usb2">This puzzle requires you to identify a code that has been hidden in the USB
    sticks provided. Find the way between them and you will be closer to the solution.</string>

</resources>
